{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Which company created JavaScript?",
            "correctAnswer": "Oracle",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript"
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
                "Netscape",
                "Krispy Kreme"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many days did it take Brendan Eich to create JavaScript?",
            "correctAnswer": "10 days",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript"
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
                "He wasn't the creator",
                "Forever"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was JavaScript originally called?",
            "correctAnswer": "Mocha",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript"
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
                "Frappucino",
                "EcmaScript"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "True or False? JavaScript is dynamically typed.",
            "correctAnswer": "True",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript"
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "True or False? Null is an object.",
            "correctAnswer": "True",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript"
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
                "False",
                "null"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "5 divided by 0 is equal to which of the following?",
            "correctAnswer": "Infinity",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript"
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
                "Undefined",
                "A pretty big number"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is a JavaScript event?",
            "correctAnswer": "onUnload",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript"
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
                "onJump",
                "onLinkClick"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "JavaScript is a subset of Java",
            "correctAnswer": "Hell no!",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript"
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
                "Hell yes!"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "True or False? Global variables are not created automatically in Strict Mode.",
            "correctAnswer": "True",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript"
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
                "False",
                "What is Strict Mode?"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Can we equate two arrays in JavaScript?",
            "correctAnswer": "Yes",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript"
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
                "No"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "True or False? JavaScript is weird.",
            "correctAnswer": "True",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript"
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": []
        },
        // thought the above question would be funny, we can get rid of it if it breaks anything lol
        {
            "question": "What do you call JavaScript without any additional frameworks or libraries?",
            "correctAnswer": "Vanilla",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript",
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
              "Plain JavaScript",
              "Chocolate JavaScript"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does each JavaScript statement need to end with?",
            "correctAnswer": "semicolon",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript",
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
              "period",
              "question mark"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the most common case used in JavaScript?",
            "correctAnswer": "Lower Camel Case",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript",
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
              "Underscore",
              "Hyphens"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What data type do you get when you add a Number and String?",
            "correctAnswer": "String",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript",
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
              "Number",
              "Stringy Number"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid data type?",
            "correctAnswer": "Array",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript",
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
              "Number",
              "String"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many basic data types are there in JavaScript?",
            "correctAnswer": "7",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript",
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
              "5",
              "10"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What data type contains the values true and false?",
            "correctAnswer": "Boolean",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript",
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
              "Binary",
              "Flag"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What do you call a block of code designed to perform a particular task?",
            "correctAnswer": "Function",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript",
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
              "Program",
              "Method"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does 'this' refer to in a function definition?",
            "correctAnswer": "The owner of the function",
            "tags": [
                "JavaScript",
            ],
            "wrongAnswer": [
              "A confusing question",
              "Not 'that'"
            ]
        },
    ]
}
